<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<pmxi_records><node>
		<product_id><![CDATA[prod5090002]]></product_id>
		<display_name><![CDATA[Rigid Industries ADAPT E-Series LED Light Bars]]></display_name>
		<long_desc><![CDATA[Harness, switch and relay included;3 Optic Zones - Scene, driving, spot;Seamless beam transition;Slow speed, moderate speed and high speed beam patterns;9-36 VDC;Two layers of adaptive response;Active Power Management System - Power capacity sensing;Active View Technology - Internal GPS module;Use in Adapt mode or all on;Limited lifetime warranty;Alloy housing and heatsink;Unbreakable polycarbonate lens;Pressure equalizing vent;Black exposed printed circuit board;Patented optics;50,000 Hr+ LED lifespan;Off road use only]]></long_desc>
		<sales_desc><![CDATA[The RIGID Adapt E-Series takes off-road lighting performance to a whole new level with two layers of adaptive response to your vehicle and driving conditions. The first layer of adaptive response is RIGID's new Active Power Management (APM) system which continuously monitors input voltage to determine the status of the vehicle's electrical system. If the voltage is stable, the Adapt E-Series will continue to utilize all available power to give you the most output possible. If the available voltage to the light begins to drop due to insufficient power, RIGID's APM system will gradually reduce the light's power consumption until the vehicle's voltage stabilizes.The second layer of adaptive response featured in the Adapt E-Series is RIGID's proven Active View Technology. This technology uses an internal GPS module to determine the vehicle's speed, allowing the Adapt E-Series to properly distribute all available power among three unique optic zones. Utilizing the three zones allows the Active View Technology to create the most optimal beam pattern to suit the vehicle's speed. As the vehicle's speed changes, power is dynamically routed through various optics. Utilizing scene optics for low speed, driving optics for moderate speed and spot optics for high speed driving. This allows for a seamless transition between beam patterns offered in the Adapt E-Series making it easier than ever to Own The Night]]></sales_desc>
	</node><node>
		<product_id><![CDATA[prod7520003]]></product_id>
		<display_name><![CDATA[Pilot Blind Spot Mirrors]]></display_name>
		<long_desc><![CDATA[Universal;Convex;Adhesive back;Quality finish;Packaged well to protect product]]></long_desc>
		<sales_desc><![CDATA[Eliminate drivers blind spots with Pilots Blind Spot Mirror, which easily mounts on to the driver and passenger side mirror. This is a great addition to your vehicle that will enhance your driving experience. Mirror effectively increase viewing angle for ultimate safety.]]></sales_desc>
	</node><node>
		<product_id><![CDATA[prod7520004]]></product_id>
		<display_name><![CDATA[Pilot LED Replacement Bulbs]]></display_name>
		<long_desc><![CDATA[Super bright 5050 SMD technology;Long life 50,000 hours of continuous use;Instant styling upgrade;Direct replacement for almost all factory applications]]></long_desc>
		<sales_desc><![CDATA[Pilot LED technology provides a bright, clean and long-lasting light for your vehicular application needs. Pilot performance LED bulbs produces more light per watt than traditional incandescent bulbs and less heat, making them the perfect upgrade for enhanced visibility, safety and creative lighting needs. LED bulbs are much more economical and efficient, lasting up to 50,000 hours, which means these are probably the last set of bulbs you'll need to buy for your vehicle! All Pilot performance LED bulbs allows for easy plug and play installation.]]></sales_desc>
	</node><node>
		<product_id><![CDATA[prod7520005]]></product_id>
		<display_name><![CDATA[Pilot Light Switches]]></display_name>
		<long_desc><![CDATA[Universal 12 volt switch;Made out of ABS plastic;Easy installation]]></long_desc>
		<sales_desc><![CDATA[Pilot Automotive has been the innovator in the lighting department and it continues with the largest selection of L.E.D. lights, toggle switches and harness kits in the industry. L.E.D. lights are used to light up everything from stereo systems, wheels on your ride, interiors, exteriors and even engine compartments. Every kit comes complete with wiring diagrams and mounting instructions. Now you can change the look of your showpiece with hardy and effort and light up the night.]]></sales_desc>
	</node><node>
		<product_id><![CDATA[prod7520001]]></product_id>
		<display_name><![CDATA[Oracle Lighting LED Strobe Lights]]></display_name>
		<long_desc><![CDATA[Input: 12V-24V;Wattage: 2W;LED: 4x 0.5W;Width: 1;Length: 3.75";Height: .12";Lifetime: 100,000 hours;Flush mount design;ECE R10 Class 1 certification;19 different flash patterns"]]></long_desc>
		<sales_desc><![CDATA[Oracle Lighting is proud to serve First Responders and Law Enforcement Officers and these strobe lights will not disappoint! Using the latest in solid-state LED technology these Super-Bright LED strobe lights blow away the competition. The built in controller module allows you to select 19 different patterns without the need of an external LED controller. Internal electronics are fully encapsulated for extended product life.]]></sales_desc>
	</node><node>
		<product_id><![CDATA[prod7520002]]></product_id>
		<display_name><![CDATA[Pilot LED Light Strips]]></display_name>
		<long_desc><![CDATA[Sealed housing;Interior and exterior use;100 percent water proof;Easy peel and stick]]></long_desc>
		<sales_desc><![CDATA[Pilot Automotive LED light is a LED light that is a must have accessory to highlight virtually anything and everything on your vehicle offering that high end look. It has a long lasting LED that has a life of over 100,000 hours and can be easily mounted on the interior surfaces of your vehicle. The thin design of this product allows easy installation and the lens design collects and distributes LED light giving a simulated neon look.]]></sales_desc>
	</node><node>
		<product_id><![CDATA[prod1570007]]></product_id>
		<display_name><![CDATA[B&W Hitch Gooseneck Hitch Mounting Kits]]></display_name>
		<long_desc><![CDATA[]]></long_desc>
		<sales_desc><![CDATA[B&W Trailer Hitches products are designed using advanced manufacturing techniques to meet and exceed your highest expectations. Crafted from sturdy materials with the greatest care and precision they ensure a high level of quality you expect from B&W Trailer Hitches. Manufactured in a state-of-the-art facility by expert professionals using the technologically advanced equipment B&W products are durable and strong. When it comes to uncompromising reliability, you can rely on B&W Trailer Hitches.]]></sales_desc>
	</node><node>
		<product_id><![CDATA[prod1570006]]></product_id>
		<display_name><![CDATA[B&W Hitch Turnoverball Gooseneck Hitches]]></display_name>
		<long_desc><![CDATA[]]></long_desc>
		<sales_desc><![CDATA[B&W Trailer Hitches products are designed using advanced manufacturing techniques to meet and exceed your highest expectations. Crafted from sturdy materials with the greatest care and precision they ensure a high level of quality you expect from B&W Trailer Hitches. Manufactured in a state-of-the-art facility by expert professionals using the technologically advanced equipment B&W products are durable and strong. When it comes to uncompromising reliability, you can rely on B&W Trailer Hitches.]]></sales_desc>
	</node><node>
		<product_id><![CDATA[prod1570012]]></product_id>
		<display_name><![CDATA[B&W Hitch Beacon Brackets]]></display_name>
		<long_desc><![CDATA[]]></long_desc>
		<sales_desc><![CDATA[B&W Trailer Hitches products are designed using advanced manufacturing techniques to meet and exceed your highest expectations. Crafted from sturdy materials with the greatest care and precision they ensure a high level of quality you expect from B&W Trailer Hitches. Manufactured in a state-of-the-art facility by expert professionals using the technologically advanced equipment B&W products are durable and strong. When it comes to uncompromising reliability, you can rely on B&W Trailer Hitches.]]></sales_desc>
	</node><node>
		<product_id><![CDATA[prod1570011]]></product_id>
		<display_name><![CDATA[B&W Hitch Light Bar Mounting Kits]]></display_name>
		<long_desc><![CDATA[]]></long_desc>
		<sales_desc><![CDATA[B&W Trailer Hitches products are designed using advanced manufacturing techniques to meet and exceed your highest expectations. Crafted from sturdy materials with the greatest care and precision they ensure a high level of quality you expect from B&W Trailer Hitches. Manufactured in a state-of-the-art facility by expert professionals using the technologically advanced equipment B&W products are durable and strong. When it comes to uncompromising reliability, you can rely on B&W Trailer Hitches.]]></sales_desc>
	</node><node>
		<product_id><![CDATA[prod1600070]]></product_id>
		<display_name><![CDATA[KMC XD Series XD137 FMJ Wheels - Satin Black]]></display_name>
		<long_desc><![CDATA[]]></long_desc>
		<sales_desc><![CDATA[Strength when needed, speed when necessary, show-stopping style always. The FMJ has a concave eight-spoke, D-window design with dual simulated rim locks in a dramatic step down orientation. You can go with the powerful, yet understated Satin Black finish, or the more aggressive Satin Black With Dark Tinted Clear Coat, featuring a satin red center insert.]]></sales_desc>
	</node><node>
		<product_id><![CDATA[prod1600071]]></product_id>
		<display_name><![CDATA[KMC XD Series XD137 FMJ Wheels - Satin Black with Dark Tinted Clear Coat]]></display_name>
		<long_desc><![CDATA[]]></long_desc>
		<sales_desc><![CDATA[Strength when needed, speed when necessary, show-stopping style always. The FMJ has a concave eight-spoke, D-window design with dual simulated rim locks in a dramatic step down orientation. You can go with the powerful, yet understated Satin Black finish, or the more aggressive Satin Black With Dark Tinted Clear Coat, featuring a satin red center insert.]]></sales_desc>
	</node><node>
		<product_id><![CDATA[prod1600072]]></product_id>
		<display_name><![CDATA[KMC XD Series XD837 Demodog Wheels - Gloss Black Milled]]></display_name>
		<long_desc><![CDATA[]]></long_desc>
		<sales_desc><![CDATA[Whether you are looking at it from the upside-down or not, the Demodog has a futuristic five-spoke mesh design with a dauntless and intrepid style that refuses to go unnoticed. The lip is highly detailed with milling and design elements and the center incorporates a modern, race-inspired simulated beadring with a machined undercut. Included are both black and red brushed and anodized center cap rings to add level of customization.]]></sales_desc>
	</node><node>
		<product_id><![CDATA[prod1600073]]></product_id>
		<display_name><![CDATA[KMC XD Series XD837 Demodog Wheels - Satin Black with Gray Tinted Clear Coat]]></display_name>
		<long_desc><![CDATA[]]></long_desc>
		<sales_desc><![CDATA[Whether you are looking at it from the upside-down or not, the Demodog has a futuristic five-spoke mesh design with a dauntless and intrepid style that refuses to go unnoticed. The lip is highly detailed with milling and design elements and the center incorporates a modern, race-inspired simulated beadring with a machined undercut. Included are both black and red brushed and anodized center cap rings to add level of customization.]]></sales_desc>
	</node><node>
		<product_id><![CDATA[prod1600074]]></product_id>
		<display_name><![CDATA[KMC XD Series XD839 Clamp Wheels - Gloss Black Milled]]></display_name>
		<long_desc><![CDATA[]]></long_desc>
		<sales_desc><![CDATA[Modern refinement with futuristic design. On one hand, the Clamp's split five-spoke construction screams classic muscle car while on the other, the center cap has a powerful, chunky, off-road feel. Both combine in a mid-lip wheel with plenty of negative space and dense detail. For further customization, both red and black center cap rings are included.]]></sales_desc>
	</node><node>
		<product_id><![CDATA[prod1600075]]></product_id>
		<display_name><![CDATA[KMC XD Series XD839 Clamp Wheels - Chrome]]></display_name>
		<long_desc><![CDATA[]]></long_desc>
		<sales_desc><![CDATA[Modern refinement with futuristic design. On one hand, the Clamp's split five-spoke construction screams classic muscle car while on the other, the center cap has a powerful, chunky, off-road feel. Both combine in a mid-lip wheel with plenty of negative space and dense detail. For further customization, both red and black center cap rings are included.]]></sales_desc>
	</node><node>
		<product_id><![CDATA[prod1600068]]></product_id>
		<display_name><![CDATA[KMC Wheels KM710 Takedown Wheels]]></display_name>
		<long_desc><![CDATA[]]></long_desc>
		<sales_desc><![CDATA[KMC wheels Like no other". KMC rims are in a League of their own. A must see line of wheels. Every style has enormous detail, you get what you pay for and with KMC wheels, its evident. We truly love selling these beautiful styles from KMC wheels. KMC Produces some of the hottest wheels on the market. Be sure to check out the wide variety of styles and sizes they have to offer. Hubcentric Ring included where applicable."]]></sales_desc>
	</node><node>
		<product_id><![CDATA[prod1600069]]></product_id>
		<display_name><![CDATA[KMC XD Series XD136 Panzer Wheels - Satin Black]]></display_name>
		<long_desc><![CDATA[]]></long_desc>
		<sales_desc><![CDATA[We wouldn't roll into battle in anything less than a tank. Get your ride ready for action with the Panzer. The heavy-duty industrial design is both extremely solid and ruggedly utilitarian. Twenty circular cut-throughs set deeper than the rest of the center, combined with dual race inspired bead locks beg for a second look.]]></sales_desc>
	</node><node>
		<product_id><![CDATA[prod1600066]]></product_id>
		<display_name><![CDATA[Helo HE908 Gloss Black Wheels]]></display_name>
		<long_desc><![CDATA[]]></long_desc>
		<sales_desc><![CDATA[Helo Wheels give you that custom street look for stock, lowered or lifted trucks and SUV's. Quality, multiple choices to choose from and a variety of finishes available. Hubcentric Ring included where applicable.]]></sales_desc>
	</node><node>
		<product_id><![CDATA[prod1600067]]></product_id>
		<display_name><![CDATA[Helo HE908 Chrome Wheels]]></display_name>
		<long_desc><![CDATA[]]></long_desc>
		<sales_desc><![CDATA[Helo Wheels give you that custom street look for stock, lowered or lifted trucks and SUV's. Quality, multiple choices to choose from and a variety of finishes available. Hubcentric Ring included where applicable.]]></sales_desc>
	</node><node>
		<product_id><![CDATA[prod3570001]]></product_id>
		<display_name><![CDATA[Baja Designs XL Laser LED Lights]]></display_name>
		<long_desc><![CDATA[uService - Replaceable lenses and optics;ClearView - All the light, right where you need it;MoistureBlock - Waterproof, rain proof, submersible;CopperDrive - Only LED driven at 100%;Lumens: 2,000 Utilizing 4 Laser Chips;Wattage/Amps: 60w;Dimensions: 4.43 x 3.65" x 4.43";Weight: 2.45 lbs;Laser Chip Life Expectancy: 2000;Front Lens: Hard Coated Polycarbonate;Housing: Aircraft Grade Aluminum w/Mil-Spec Hard Anodize;Bezel: Billet Machined Aluminum;Hardware and Bracket Material: Stainless Steel;Exceeds MIL-STD810G (Mil-Spec Testing);Built-in overvoltage protection;IP69K (Waterproof up to 9ft and Pressure Washable);IK10 Compliant (Mechanical Impact Testing)"]]></long_desc>
		<sales_desc><![CDATA[The XL Laser light is the World's first laser auxiliary light and has redefined the future of forward projection lighting. Capable of throwing light an astonishing 350% farther than our current XL Racer Edition, the XL Laser is the most effective distance light available today. Projecting four laser chips through our proprietary High Speed Spot optic, this light produces an extremely tight 1.5 pattern, and distance that is untouchable by any LED or HID platform. If your truck, jeep, or UTV requires the ultimate in distance lighting look no further than the XL Laser.]]></sales_desc>
	</node><node>
		<product_id><![CDATA[prod3570010]]></product_id>
		<display_name><![CDATA[Holley Performance EFI Avenger Fuel Injection System]]></display_name>
		<long_desc><![CDATA[Self-tuning fueling strategy tunes while you drive - Designed for the user that wants ease of use without having to be a ?tuning expert;<b>California Residents: <a href=/prop65" target="_blank">WARNING</a></b>"]]></long_desc>
		<sales_desc><![CDATA[Self-tuning fueling strategy tunes while you drive - Designed for the user that wants ease of use without having to be a ?tuning expert]]></sales_desc>
	</node><node>
		<product_id><![CDATA[prod5660010]]></product_id>
		<display_name><![CDATA[RockJock 4x4 Tie Rod Ends]]></display_name>
		<long_desc><![CDATA[]]></long_desc>
		<sales_desc><![CDATA[The RockJock Currectlync tie rod end installs at the driver's side end of the tie rod and includes the boot, nut, cotter pin & zerk fitting.]]></sales_desc>
	</node><node>
		<product_id><![CDATA[prod5660009]]></product_id>
		<display_name><![CDATA[RockJock 4x4 Track Bar Bushings]]></display_name>
		<long_desc><![CDATA[]]></long_desc>
		<sales_desc><![CDATA[]]></sales_desc>
	</node><node>
		<product_id><![CDATA[prod5660007]]></product_id>
		<display_name><![CDATA[XD XD851 Monster 3 Black / Gray Wheels]]></display_name>
		<long_desc><![CDATA[]]></long_desc>
		<sales_desc><![CDATA[XD wheels rip through limits. They thrive on the dirt and chaos of extra-duty, off-road racing. They are built for those who need precise equipment for an imprecise environment. Light- weight, strong, and race-tested, these wheels are always looking to take on the next challenge.]]></sales_desc>
	</node><node>
		<product_id><![CDATA[prod5660008]]></product_id>
		<display_name><![CDATA[XD XD851 Monster 3 Black Wheels]]></display_name>
		<long_desc><![CDATA[]]></long_desc>
		<sales_desc><![CDATA[XD wheels rip through limits. They thrive on the dirt and chaos of extra-duty, off-road racing. They are built for those who need precise equipment for an imprecise environment. Light- weight, strong, and race-tested, these wheels are always looking to take on the next challenge.]]></sales_desc>
	</node><node>
		<product_id><![CDATA[prod5660005]]></product_id>
		<display_name><![CDATA[XD XD847 Outbreak Black / Milled Wheels]]></display_name>
		<long_desc><![CDATA[]]></long_desc>
		<sales_desc><![CDATA[XD wheels rip through limits. They thrive on the dirt and chaos of extra-duty, off-road racing. They are built for those who need precise equipment for an imprecise environment. Light- weight, strong, and race-tested, these wheels are always looking to take on the next challenge.]]></sales_desc>
	</node><node>
		<product_id><![CDATA[prod5660006]]></product_id>
		<display_name><![CDATA[XD XD849 Grenade 2 Black / Milled Wheels]]></display_name>
		<long_desc><![CDATA[]]></long_desc>
		<sales_desc><![CDATA[XD wheels rip through limits. They thrive on the dirt and chaos of extra-duty, off-road racing. They are built for those who need precise equipment for an imprecise environment. Light- weight, strong, and race-tested, these wheels are always looking to take on the next challenge.]]></sales_desc>
	</node><node>
		<product_id><![CDATA[prod5660003]]></product_id>
		<display_name><![CDATA[XD XD846 Double Deuce Black Wheels]]></display_name>
		<long_desc><![CDATA[]]></long_desc>
		<sales_desc><![CDATA[XD wheels rip through limits. They thrive on the dirt and chaos of extra-duty, off-road racing. They are built for those who need precise equipment for an imprecise environment. Light- weight, strong, and race-tested, these wheels are always looking to take on the next challenge.]]></sales_desc>
	</node><node>
		<product_id><![CDATA[prod5660004]]></product_id>
		<display_name><![CDATA[XD XD847 Outbreak Black / Gray Wheels]]></display_name>
		<long_desc><![CDATA[]]></long_desc>
		<sales_desc><![CDATA[XD wheels rip through limits. They thrive on the dirt and chaos of extra-duty, off-road racing. They are built for those who need precise equipment for an imprecise environment. Light- weight, strong, and race-tested, these wheels are always looking to take on the next challenge.]]></sales_desc>
	</node><node>
		<product_id><![CDATA[prod5660001]]></product_id>
		<display_name><![CDATA[XD XD838 Mammoth Black / Milled / Red Wheels]]></display_name>
		<long_desc><![CDATA[]]></long_desc>
		<sales_desc><![CDATA[With impressive stature and solid design, the Mammoth's symmetrical look manifests lasting prudence and determination. The column-like, deep milled eight-spoke design resides in a deep lip, milled-edge rim. Stoic and straightforward, the Mammoth accentuates clean lines and bold geometric shapes. For a crisp look, go with the Chrome option, or for a more dynamic statement, the Gloss Black Milled finish.<br><br>Features<br>- Deep lip, eight-spoke design<br>- Heavy two-surface milling<br>- New spot milled lip<br>- Covered center cap for dual drilled applications]]></sales_desc>
	</node><node>
		<product_id><![CDATA[prod5660002]]></product_id>
		<display_name><![CDATA[XD XD846 Double Deuce Black / Dark Tint Wheels]]></display_name>
		<long_desc><![CDATA[]]></long_desc>
		<sales_desc><![CDATA[XD wheels rip through limits. They thrive on the dirt and chaos of extra-duty, off-road racing. They are built for those who need precise equipment for an imprecise environment. Light- weight, strong, and race-tested, these wheels are always looking to take on the next challenge.]]></sales_desc>
	</node><node>
		<product_id><![CDATA[prod7110002]]></product_id>
		<display_name><![CDATA[Rough Country Shock Bar Pin Eliminator Kits]]></display_name>
		<long_desc><![CDATA[Easy bolt-on installation;Stronger mount than the factory bar pin setup;Eliminates rattling noises produced by the factory bar pin mount;Replaces the front lower bar pin shock mount]]></long_desc>
		<sales_desc><![CDATA[Bar Pin Eliminators eliminate rattle and thumping sound you hear from the floorboard. This kit allows the bushings to fill the shock loop eye completely in the front lower shock mount, reducing any irritating noises.]]></sales_desc>
	</node><node>
		<product_id><![CDATA[prod890054]]></product_id>
		<display_name><![CDATA[Smittybilt Exoskeletons]]></display_name>
		<long_desc><![CDATA[Four crossbars for rack/tent mounting that are removeable for soft top or hardtop removal;Mounts directly on to vehicle body;Front and rear integrated light mounting tabs;Front brackets can accommodate two 50 LED light bars;Powder coat finish - 5 year limited warranty;Smittybilt limited lifetime warranty;<b>California Residents: <a href="/prop65" target="_blank">WARNING</a></b>"]]></long_desc>
		<sales_desc><![CDATA[Smittybilt's new Exoskeleton fends off rocks and obstacles to keep your sheetmetal straight. The 1.75-inch diameter, 0.120-wall tubing is thick enough to prevent damage, yet the entire exoskeleton only weighs 70 pounds, minimizing the effects on your Jeep's handling and performance.]]></sales_desc>
	</node><node>
		<product_id><![CDATA[prod910002]]></product_id>
		<display_name><![CDATA[Omix-Ada Fender Flare Support Brackets]]></display_name>
		<long_desc><![CDATA[Direct OE replacement Jeep parts and accessories built to the original specifications by Rugged Ridge;Support bracket uses factory hardware and offers a direct fit with no drilling required;<b>California Residents: <a href=/prop65" target="_blank">WARNING</a></b>"]]></long_desc>
		<sales_desc><![CDATA[]]></sales_desc>
	</node><node>
		<product_id><![CDATA[prod3550001]]></product_id>
		<display_name><![CDATA[Rough Country Suspension Lift Kits]]></display_name>
		<long_desc><![CDATA[Gain increased ground clearance and incredible good looks with a kit from Rough Country;Most kits come with everything you need to overhaul your Truck or Jeep's appearance while maintaining a factory-like ride quality;Most kits include Rough Country's N3 Shocks;These 10-stage variable valving, high-pressure Nitrogen charged shocks offer a fantastic blend of off-road action and smooth highway ride quality;Durable 18mm spring-loaded piston rod and faster-cooling 54mm shock body;Includes Rough Country's Lifetime Replacement Guarantee!]]></long_desc>
		<sales_desc><![CDATA[Rough Country Suspension Lift Kits offer amazing off-road performance at an incredible value. Whether you're looking to run larger tires, give your vehicle a more aggressive look, or achieve outstanding performance on the trails, Rough Country has the right lift kit for your Jeep, Truck, or SUV. Rough Country Lift Kits are easy-to-install and backed by our Lifetime Replacement Guarantee!]]></sales_desc>
	</node><node>
		<product_id><![CDATA[prod4540001]]></product_id>
		<display_name><![CDATA[WeatherTech Hood Protectors]]></display_name>
		<long_desc><![CDATA[Stylish skin-tight fit;Designed to flow with the contours of each vehicle's hood;Flush mounted;Flexible, durable, acrylic material;Can be removed without damaging your vehicle's paint finish]]></long_desc>
		<sales_desc><![CDATA[The Hood Protector allows for ultimate protection through its sleek, low profile polished finish. The Hood Protector is made from a durable, yet flexible acrylic that withstands the wear-and-tear from the daily grind. Through its exclusive, custom-fit design, the Hood Protector follows the hood's contours with a wrap design that provides a sleek, aerodynamically-friendly finish.<br><br>By providing a barrier against bugs and debris, the Hood Protector helps to preserve and maintain your vehicle's paint finishes. The Hood Protector mounts in minutes using strong 3M automotive tape without the need for drilling. The product is available in a dark smoke finish and is made in the USA.]]></sales_desc>
	</node><node>
		<product_id><![CDATA[prod4540003]]></product_id>
		<display_name><![CDATA[Maxxis Bighorn 3.0 Tires]]></display_name>
		<long_desc><![CDATA[]]></long_desc>
		<sales_desc><![CDATA[Based on the legendary Bighorn and Bighorn 2.0, the Bighorn 3.0 features a 6-ply rated radial construction with maneuverability and durability. It boasts tremendous grip and a smooth ride with a large contact patch.<br><br>- Front and rear specific<br>- Radial construction provides a plush feel and a large contact patch for the ultimate ride<br>- Based on the legendary Bighorn and Bighorn 2.0]]></sales_desc>
	</node><node>
		<product_id><![CDATA[prod4540002]]></product_id>
		<display_name><![CDATA[Toyo Open Country SxS Tires]]></display_name>
		<long_desc><![CDATA[]]></long_desc>
		<sales_desc><![CDATA[The Open Country SxS delivers performance and design features of the race-winning Open Country M/T-R in a smaller package specifically designed for side-by-side vehicles. A 32 diameter provides high ground clearance for tackling obstacles. Durable construction and advanced compounds developed through strenuous motorsports testing provide responsive off-road traction on rocky paths, muddy trails, and uneven surfaces."]]></sales_desc>
	</node><node>
		<product_id><![CDATA[prod4540007]]></product_id>
		<display_name><![CDATA[Maxxis Roxxzilla Tires]]></display_name>
		<long_desc><![CDATA[]]></long_desc>
		<sales_desc><![CDATA[The Roxxzilla is the premier SxS rock crawling tire! With 8-ply-rated radial construction, multi-layer sidewall design, stepped shoulder lugs and a soft tread compound, the Roxxzilla is the perfect tire for gripping rock. When mounting oversized tires to your ATV or SxS, be sure to check for proper fitment and tire clearance.<br><br>- 8-ply-rated radial construction<br>- Soft rock crawling tread compound<br>- High void-ratio in center and two layers on shoulder improve grip and puncture resistance<br>- High multi-layer sidewall design enhances sidewall traction for rock crawling<br>- *Denotes Competition Compound]]></sales_desc>
	</node><node>
		<product_id><![CDATA[prod4540006]]></product_id>
		<display_name><![CDATA[Maxxis Liberty Tires]]></display_name>
		<long_desc><![CDATA[]]></long_desc>
		<sales_desc><![CDATA[The Liberty is engineered for performance to give you and your side-by-side freedom in a variety of terrains.<br><br>The Maxxis Liberty is a true light truck-inspired tire, engineered for performance in a variety of terrains. With an 8-ply radial carcass and a tread design that allows for ultimate control on and off-road, the Liberty exceeds DOT test standards and has the superb tread wear you expect from a Maxxis tire. This tire also features a specialized rubber compound for excellent traction on rocks and desert terrains. Eight-ply radial construction lets the Liberty withstand the heavier loads and high speeds of your largest SxS machines.<br><br>- ML3<br>- Exceeds DOT Test Standards<br>- 8-Ply Radial Construction<br>- Specialized Rubber Compound for Supreme Traction and Control<br>- Excellent Tread Wear<br>- Podium Proven (2015 Baja 500)]]></sales_desc>
	</node><node>
		<product_id><![CDATA[prod4540005]]></product_id>
		<display_name><![CDATA[Maxxis Carnivore Tires]]></display_name>
		<long_desc><![CDATA[]]></long_desc>
		<sales_desc><![CDATA[8-ply-rated, light truck-inspired tire engineered to perform in extreme terrains.<br><br>The Carnivore is a true light truck-inspired tire, engineered for performance in extreme (west coast) terrains. With an 8-ply-rated radial carcass and a tread design that allows for ultimate control on and off-road, the Carnivore has the superb tread wear you expect from a Maxxis tire. This tire also features a specialized rubber compound for excellent traction on rocks, roots and desert terrains.<br><br>- 8-ply-rated radial construction<br>- Specialized rubber compound for supreme traction and control<br>- Superb tread wear<br>- Excellent for extreme terrains]]></sales_desc>
	</node><node>
		<product_id><![CDATA[prod4540004]]></product_id>
		<display_name><![CDATA[Maxxis Coronado Tires]]></display_name>
		<long_desc><![CDATA[]]></long_desc>
		<sales_desc><![CDATA[An 8PR carcass and aggressive tread pattern make this the ultimate utility tire, whether for backcountry jaunts or national races.<br><br>The Maxxis Coronado is the ultimate desert tire for your ATV or side-by-side. Brutal desert terrains are no match for the Coronado's long-wearing compound, formulated for high speeds and high temperatures. The tire's strong 8-ply rated radial carcass soaks up the shock from rocks and sand whoops for ultimate control, and ensures maximum puncture resistance in the face of thorns and sharp rocks. The Maxxis Coronado's aggressive tread pattern extends well over the shoulder area for increased sidewall protection and features stepped lugs to provide multiple biting edges. Steering performance is maximized by a rounded front tire profile that hooks up on flat turns and stays in ruts when necessary.<br><br>- The Coronado features an 8PR radial carcass designed for supreme performance and longevity<br>- Tread pattern features stepped lugs and a long-wearing compound optimized for loose-over-hard desert terrains<br>- Performance-matched front and rear setup provides steering control and confidence at high speeds<br>- A smooth ride stemming from true radial construction and a center tread configuration with a high land-to-sea ratio of lugs]]></sales_desc>
	</node><node>
		<product_id><![CDATA[prod4680001]]></product_id>
		<display_name><![CDATA[PSC Steering Adapters and Fittings]]></display_name>
		<long_desc><![CDATA[]]></long_desc>
		<sales_desc><![CDATA[]]></sales_desc>
	</node><node>
		<product_id><![CDATA[prod4720017]]></product_id>
		<display_name><![CDATA[Body Armor 4x4 Tow Strap]]></display_name>
		<long_desc><![CDATA[Multiple color finish;100% Polyester;Sewn in strap preventing unraveling;Protective sleeve included]]></long_desc>
		<sales_desc><![CDATA[Body Armor 44 was founded over ten years ago with the vision to provide high quality durable products for the off-road community. Their products are engineered to stand up to abuse and function while enhancing the looks of the vehicle that they are installed on. At Body Armor 44 we are committed to providing innovative products for the off-road enthusiast.]]></sales_desc>
	</node><node>
		<product_id><![CDATA[prod1480113]]></product_id>
		<display_name><![CDATA[K&N Heavy Duty Canister Air Filters]]></display_name>
		<long_desc><![CDATA[]]></long_desc>
		<sales_desc><![CDATA[]]></sales_desc>
	</node><node>
		<product_id><![CDATA[prod1480124]]></product_id>
		<display_name><![CDATA[WeatherTech Cargo Liners with Bumper Protector]]></display_name>
		<long_desc><![CDATA[Interior protection from all types of wear and tear;Custom molded specifically for your application;High outside lip helps contain spills;Quick and easy cleanup;A skid-resistant surface;Protects and preserves the cargo area and trunk carpet;Engineered for toughness and durability;Easy installation]]></long_desc>
		<sales_desc><![CDATA[The WeatherTech Bumper Protector is a great addition to your Cargo Liner to help protect the surface of your vehicle's bumper from dings and scratches when loading or unloading personal items or pets. The Bumper Protector is made from highly durable vinyl fabric that easily snaps onto your Cargo Liner by stainless, rust resistant snaps.]]></sales_desc>
	</node><node>
		<product_id><![CDATA[prod1780003]]></product_id>
		<display_name><![CDATA[Rugged Ridge Tie Rod End Dust Boot]]></display_name>
		<long_desc><![CDATA[]]></long_desc>
		<sales_desc><![CDATA[]]></sales_desc>
	</node><node>
		<product_id><![CDATA[prod1780001]]></product_id>
		<display_name><![CDATA[Wilco Offroad Tow Hook Light Bars]]></display_name>
		<long_desc><![CDATA[]]></long_desc>
		<sales_desc><![CDATA[]]></sales_desc>
	</node><node>
		<product_id><![CDATA[prod7790001]]></product_id>
		<display_name><![CDATA[Camburg Engineering Front Bumper]]></display_name>
		<long_desc><![CDATA[Available powdercoated textured black;Steel construction;Some come with an 3/16 aluminum skid plate;Incorporated shackle D-ring mounts tied into main structure for optimum strength;Updated to accept factory front parking sonar sensors (Filler caps included) - most models;Includes all necessary grade 8 hardware;Fits with factory sheet metal fenders and also long-travel fiberglass fenders;Bumper ships truck freight due to size and weight;Made in the USA"]]></long_desc>
		<sales_desc><![CDATA[Camburg front bumpers are one of the most thought out and engineered designs on the market. Camburg spent countless hours CAD designing and prototyping getting it to this point. This wasn't something thrown together overnight. Camburg has close to a year developing and testing this product prior to releasing it to the public. It's unique modular design aids installation and gives you the ability to customize and also replace components if ever damaged.]]></sales_desc>
	</node><node>
		<product_id><![CDATA[prod1670007]]></product_id>
		<display_name><![CDATA[Smittybilt Recovery Rope Storage Bags]]></display_name>
		<long_desc><![CDATA[]]></long_desc>
		<sales_desc><![CDATA[]]></sales_desc>
	</node><node>
		<product_id><![CDATA[prod1670005]]></product_id>
		<display_name><![CDATA[Warn 12-18K Hydraulic Series Industrial Winches]]></display_name>
		<long_desc><![CDATA[Rated Line Pull = 12,000 to 18,000 lbs. options;Motor = 3.0, 5.0 and 7.3 Cubic In. applications;Horse Power = N/A;Remote Control: = None - Hydraulic Winch;Wire Rope = Optional -max. 1/2;Fairlead = None;Type of Winch = Hydraulic;<b>California Residents: <a href=/prop65" target="_blank">WARNING</a></b>"]]></long_desc>
		<sales_desc><![CDATA[Top selling model ideally suited for tow, utility and trailer applications. Heavy-duty disc brake for dependable operation and plenty of holding power. Meets SAE J706 and CE specifications. Wire rope, roller fairlead, and tensioner sold separately.]]></sales_desc>
	</node><node>
		<product_id><![CDATA[prod1670006]]></product_id>
		<display_name><![CDATA[Warn 8-10K Hydraulic Series Industrial Winches]]></display_name>
		<long_desc><![CDATA[Rated Line Pull = 8,000 to 10,500 lbs. options;Motor = 3.0, 5.0 and 7.3 Cubic In. applications;Horse Power = N/A;Remote Control: = None - Hydraulic Winch;Wire Rope = Optional -max. 1/2;Fairlead = None;Type of Winch = Hydraulic;<b>California Residents: <a href=/prop65" target="_blank">WARNING</a></b>"]]></long_desc>
		<sales_desc><![CDATA[Top selling model ideally suited for tow, utility and trailer applications. Heavy-duty disc brake for dependable operation and plenty of holding power. Meets SAE J706 and CE specifications. Wire rope, roller fairlead, and tensioner sold separately.]]></sales_desc>
	</node><node>
		<product_id><![CDATA[prod1670010]]></product_id>
		<display_name><![CDATA[Rubicon Express Super-Ride Suspenion Lift Kits]]></display_name>
		<long_desc><![CDATA[Available with or without shocks;1.75 diameter 4130 chromoly Super-Ride front lower arms;Extended sway bar end links and extended bump stops;<b>California Residents: <a href="/prop65" target="_blank">WARNING</a></b>"]]></long_desc>
		<sales_desc><![CDATA[This easy to install system elevates the new JL's ride quality and off-road performance.  Coil spring rates are perfectly tuned for bump compliance and load handling and are complemented by 2.5 diameter floating piston monotube shocks. These shocks are precisely tuned by Rubicon Express to maximize all terrain comfort, overall driver control and stability. Detail features include 1.75" diameter 4130 chromoly Super-Ride front lower arms, extended sway bar end links and extended bump stops to boost off-road capability.  This highly tuned system will provide the right height to clear 35" tires on a loaded non-Rubicon models and 37" tires on Rubicon models."]]></sales_desc>
	</node><node>
		<product_id><![CDATA[prod1670009]]></product_id>
		<display_name><![CDATA[Pro Comp Shock Extensions]]></display_name>
		<long_desc><![CDATA[Front and rear shock extensions;Bolt-on installation;<b>California Residents: <a href=/prop65" target="_blank">WARNING</a></b>"]]></long_desc>
		<sales_desc><![CDATA[Pro Comp is proud to announce the release of 2-2.5 heavy-duty, bolt-on shock extensions to retain the stock shock absorbers for a same as factory ride."]]></sales_desc>
	</node><node>
		<product_id><![CDATA[prod2500002]]></product_id>
		<display_name><![CDATA[Alloy USA Outer Stub Axle Shafts]]></display_name>
		<long_desc><![CDATA[]]></long_desc>
		<sales_desc><![CDATA[]]></sales_desc>
	</node><node>
		<product_id><![CDATA[prod2500001]]></product_id>
		<display_name><![CDATA[Alloy USA Inner Axle Shafts]]></display_name>
		<long_desc><![CDATA[]]></long_desc>
		<sales_desc><![CDATA[]]></sales_desc>
	</node><node>
		<product_id><![CDATA[prod4400005]]></product_id>
		<display_name><![CDATA[Bestop Racks for Sunriders]]></display_name>
		<long_desc><![CDATA[Must be ordered with the Rhino-Rack for Sunrider-Backbone in order to install;Made from reinforced nylon and aluminum;Stays attached to your hardtop even when the hardtop is removed;Stylish and aerodynamically designed to minimize wind drag and noise on the road to trail]]></long_desc>
		<sales_desc><![CDATA[Specifically designed to work with our Sunrider for Hardtop!  The Rhino-Rack for Sunrider-Pioneer Platform is the ultimate load carrying solution for your vehicle.  The sleek and stylish black powder-coated design makes life easier by allowing you to load and unlaod your gear in moments.]]></sales_desc>
	</node><node>
		<product_id><![CDATA[prod3260002]]></product_id>
		<display_name><![CDATA[FUEL Off-Road Stroke D612 Black Red Wheels]]></display_name>
		<long_desc><![CDATA[]]></long_desc>
		<sales_desc><![CDATA[Fuel wheels are available in just about any bolt pattern and offset combination. Fuel up your truck with the latest in off-road design. Whether you are on or off the road, Fuel Off-Road Wheels offer the perfect blend of style, size and application for your truck, SUV, or UTV.]]></sales_desc>
	</node><node>
		<product_id><![CDATA[prod6870001]]></product_id>
		<display_name><![CDATA[Go Rhino 1000 Series 4 Side Steps"]]></display_name>
		<long_desc><![CDATA[4 side steps;Replaceable end caps that give the steps a welded look;Convenient U-channel bracket mounting system;Available in textured black powder coat or polished stainless finish;Brackets included;Simple, no-drill installation;5-year warranty"]]></long_desc>
		<sales_desc><![CDATA[These unique 4 side steps feature a convenient u-channel mounting system and replaceable end caps for a great OE style side step at a great price. Brackets included."]]></sales_desc>
	</node><node>
		<product_id><![CDATA[prod7260010]]></product_id>
		<display_name><![CDATA[Painless Wiring Universal Trailer Wiring Pigtails]]></display_name>
		<long_desc><![CDATA[Easily add trailer wiring to your factory or Painless wiring harness;Includes with weatherpack connectors;Plug and play installation]]></long_desc>
		<sales_desc><![CDATA[Easily add trailer wiring to your factory or Painless wiring harness!  Complete with weatherpack connectors, this simple trailer wiring setup is protected from the elements.  Designed to be a plug and play installation with our pickup wiring harnesses, simply unplug the tail section connector and plug this kit in-line!]]></sales_desc>
	</node><node>
		<product_id><![CDATA[prod7260009]]></product_id>
		<display_name><![CDATA[Painless Wiring Tape and Connectors]]></display_name>
		<long_desc><![CDATA[Fleece or heat tape;Cable tie clips;Self sealing tape;Easy to apply;Cleans up loom installations without leaving a residue;Easily seals to itself for securing loom near connectors and splices]]></long_desc>
		<sales_desc><![CDATA[If you're looking for superior quality, engineering and craftsmanship, Painless is your only sensible choice. Painless has remained the leader in automotive wiring and electrical products for 30 years through engineering and innovation, not corner cutting and imitation.]]></sales_desc>
	</node><node>
		<product_id><![CDATA[prod7260008]]></product_id>
		<display_name><![CDATA[Painless Wiring ECM Units]]></display_name>
		<long_desc><![CDATA[ECM units for GM truck or Camero engines;Has the Vehicle Anti-Theft System removed;All factory emissions items]]></long_desc>
		<sales_desc><![CDATA[All factory emissions items will still be activated. You will have check engine lights until further tuning is completed. This tune is designed to allow you to start your vehicle and allow you to get it to a local tuner for further work to be completed. We do not offer this service.]]></sales_desc>
	</node><node>
		<product_id><![CDATA[prod7260014]]></product_id>
		<display_name><![CDATA[Weather Guard Bed Rat Sliding Platforms]]></display_name>
		<long_desc><![CDATA[Includes side and back panels to help prevent content loss;Heavy duty pull out platform supports 750lbs;Heavy duty rollers support maximum loads for truck bed storage or cargo van storage;Platform extends 70%;ARMOR TUF Powder Coat finish ensures years of dependability;Limited lifetime warranty ensures unparalleled quality]]></long_desc>
		<sales_desc><![CDATA[The BED RAT Sliding Platform allows you to pull the PACK RAT storage drawers toward you from the cargo area, either from the side or rear of the vehicle. The heavy-duty steel platform supports 750lbs and is ideal for truck bed storage or cargo van storage.]]></sales_desc>
	</node><node>
		<product_id><![CDATA[prod7260013]]></product_id>
		<display_name><![CDATA[DU-HA UTV All Terrain Storage Boxes]]></display_name>
		<long_desc><![CDATA[]]></long_desc>
		<sales_desc><![CDATA[]]></sales_desc>
	</node><node>
		<product_id><![CDATA[prod7260011]]></product_id>
		<display_name><![CDATA[Skyjacker UTV A-Arms]]></display_name>
		<long_desc><![CDATA[]]></long_desc>
		<sales_desc><![CDATA[]]></sales_desc>
	</node><node>
		<product_id><![CDATA[prod7260012]]></product_id>
		<display_name><![CDATA[Hypertech UTV Programmers]]></display_name>
		<long_desc><![CDATA[]]></long_desc>
		<sales_desc><![CDATA[]]></sales_desc>
	</node><node>
		<product_id><![CDATA[prod7260001]]></product_id>
		<display_name><![CDATA[Method 202 Machined Wheels]]></display_name>
		<long_desc><![CDATA[Sizes: 17;Bolt Patterns: 6 lug;Finish: Raw Machined;Max Load: 4000 lbs"]]></long_desc>
		<sales_desc><![CDATA[Method Race Wheels was created to give to the off road racing community a wheel company that makes wheels specifically for their sport. Every wheel is engineered and designed for its intended use, having been thru numerous Finite Element Analysis and field tests. Method Race Wheels have been developed to minimize weight and increase strength. The result is a wheel that is Lighter, Stronger, Faster.]]></sales_desc>
	</node><node>
		<product_id><![CDATA[prod7260002]]></product_id>
		<display_name><![CDATA[Method 101 Buggy Beadlock Machined Wheels]]></display_name>
		<long_desc><![CDATA[Size: 15 and 17";Bolt Patterns: 5 lug;Finish: Raw Machined;Max Load: 1600-3000 lbs"]]></long_desc>
		<sales_desc><![CDATA[Method Race Wheels was created to give to the off road racing community a wheel company that makes wheels specifically for their sport. Every wheel is engineered and designed for its intended use, having been thru numerous Finite Element Analysis and field tests. Method Race Wheels have been developed to minimize weight and increase strength. The result is a wheel that is Lighter, Stronger, Faster.]]></sales_desc>
	</node><node>
		<product_id><![CDATA[prod7260003]]></product_id>
		<display_name><![CDATA[Method 103 Beadlock Machined Wheels]]></display_name>
		<long_desc><![CDATA[Sizes: 15, 17";Bolt Patterns: 5, 6 lug;Finish: Raw Machined;Max Load: 1900-4000 lbs"]]></long_desc>
		<sales_desc><![CDATA[Method Race Wheels was created to give to the off road racing community a wheel company that makes wheels specifically for their sport. Every wheel is engineered and designed for its intended use, having been thru numerous Finite Element Analysis and field tests. Method Race Wheels have been developed to minimize weight and increase strength. The result is a wheel that is Lighter, Stronger, Faster.]]></sales_desc>
	</node><node>
		<product_id><![CDATA[prod7260004]]></product_id>
		<display_name><![CDATA[Method 103 HD Beadlock Machined Wheels]]></display_name>
		<long_desc><![CDATA[Sizes: 17;Botl Patterns: 6 lug;Fnish: Raw Machined;Max Load: 400 lbs"]]></long_desc>
		<sales_desc><![CDATA[Method Race Wheels was created to give to the off road racing community a wheel company that makes wheels specifically for their sport. Every wheel is engineered and designed for its intended use, having been thru numerous Finite Element Analysis and field tests. Method Race Wheels have been developed to minimize weight and increase strength. The result is a wheel that is Lighter, Stronger, Faster.]]></sales_desc>
	</node><node>
		<product_id><![CDATA[prod7260005]]></product_id>
		<display_name><![CDATA[Method 901 Matte Black Wheels]]></display_name>
		<long_desc><![CDATA[Sizes: 16;Bolt Patterns: 6 lug;Finish: Matte Black;Max Load: 3000 lbs"]]></long_desc>
		<sales_desc><![CDATA[Method Race Wheels was created to give to the off road racing community a wheel company that makes wheels specifically for their sport. Every wheel is engineered and designed for its intended use, having been thru numerous Finite Element Analysis and field tests. Method Race Wheels have been developed to minimize weight and increase strength. The result is a wheel that is Lighter, Stronger, Faster.]]></sales_desc>
	</node><node>
		<product_id><![CDATA[prod7260006]]></product_id>
		<display_name><![CDATA[Method 201 Forged Machined Wheels]]></display_name>
		<long_desc><![CDATA[Sizes: 17;Bolt Patterns: 5 lug;Finish: Raw Machined;Max Load: 4000 lbs"]]></long_desc>
		<sales_desc><![CDATA[Method Race Wheels was created to give to the off road racing community a wheel company that makes wheels specifically for their sport. Every wheel is engineered and designed for its intended use, having been thru numerous Finite Element Analysis and field tests. Method Race Wheels have been developed to minimize weight and increase strength. The result is a wheel that is Lighter, Stronger, Faster.]]></sales_desc>
	</node><node>
		<product_id><![CDATA[prod7260007]]></product_id>
		<display_name><![CDATA[Method 501 Rally Matte Black Wheels]]></display_name>
		<long_desc><![CDATA[Sizes: 17;Bolt Patterns: 5 lug;Finish: Matte Black;Max Load: 1850 lbs"]]></long_desc>
		<sales_desc><![CDATA[Method Race Wheels was created to give to the off road racing community a wheel company that makes wheels specifically for their sport. Every wheel is engineered and designed for its intended use, having been thru numerous Finite Element Analysis and field tests. Method Race Wheels have been developed to minimize weight and increase strength. The result is a wheel that is Lighter, Stronger, Faster.]]></sales_desc>
	</node></pmxi_records>